<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">parcial-1-am-acn4bv-sanchez-yegros</string>
    <string name="Text_Start">la app para mirar tus series y \npeliculas gratis!</string>
    <string name="Title_Text">Streamix.</string>
    <string name="text_home">Que te gustaría ver hoy?</string>
    <string name="textHome_pelisNuevas">Peliculas Nuevas</string>
    <string name="textHome_pelisReco">Peliculas Recomendadas</string>
    <string name="text_movieTitle">Joker</string>
    <string name="text_movieInfo">Arthur Fleck, a party clown, leads an impoverished life with his ailing mother.
        However, when society shuns him and brands him as a freak, he decides to embrace the life of crime and chaos.</string>
    <string name="text_movieTitle2">Pearl</string>
    <string name="text_movieInfoPearl">Trapped on an isolated farm, Pearl must tend to her ailing father under the watch of her mother.
        Lusting for the glamorous life she has seen in movies, Pearl temptations and repressions collide.</string>
    <string name="text_movieTitle3">Joy</string>
    <string name="text_movieInfoJoy">Following her divorce, a woman faces numerous challenges as she aims to set up a successful business empire. However,
        she manages to overcome all the odds and fulfil her dream.</string>
    <string name="text_movieTitle4">Moonlight</string>
    <string name="text_movieInfoMoonlight">Chiron, a young African-American boy, finds guidance in Juan, a drug dealer, who teaches him to carve
        his own path.</string>
    <string name="text_movieTitle5">MidSommar</string>
    <string name="text_movieInfoMid">A couple travel to Sweden to visit their friend rural hometown for
        midsummer festival, but what begins as an idyllic retreat quickly devolves into an increasingly violent and bizarre competition.</string>
    <string name="text_movieTitle6">Back to the Future</string>
    <string name="text_movieInfoBack">In the 1980s, an experiment by a weird scientist turns out to be faulty.
        It leads to his teenaged pal going back in time to the 1950s where he is forced to reunite the younger version of his parents.</string>
    <string name="contentButton">Mi Botón</string>
    <string name="button_Title">INGRESAR</string>
    <string name="Image_Start">Imagen</string>
</resources>